# **Daniel Vinson**

(650) 575-3252 390 Cypress Ave, Sunnyvale, CA

danielvinson@gmail.com Danielvinson.github.com

#### **Professional Profile**

Multidisciplinary Developer, IT Engineer, and Web Designer

#### Skills

Advanced Shell scripting on OSX and Linux. Some experience with Java/C Programming.

Knowledge with web programming including Javascript, AJAX, and Python.

Very strong troubleshooting and debugging skills.

Extremely experienced in every area of IT.

**Certifications** A+ Certified since 2002.

### **Work History**

#### QA Test Engineer at OCZ Technology

03/2012 - Present

Developed, Released and Maintain OSX/Linux platform automation software to test hardware using shell scripts and Python. Responsible for maintenance and updates for internal automation software for Windows testing.

Manage all bug reporting and testing for the Interoperability team - collect and report on all data from testing to both internal and external parties and work with Engineering or Firmware teams to ensure swift handling of bugs. Responsible for all bug Regression and Replication testing on all

Troubleshoot all internal problems in testing, including computer hardware, third party software, and internal code.

### PC/HO Sales at Best Buy

06/2011 - 03/2012

Learned computer and service sales in a team environment. Improved my knowledge on customer needs, expectations, and background knowledge. Kept up with the latest and greatest in computers, printers, networking equipment, tablets, and smart phones. Worked on my skills in teaching customers with little to no background knowledge how to do some of the coolest things in technology.

## **Technician at Help Desk Computers**

05/2009 - 02/2011

On-site and remote support and installation of servers, networks, and PCs for residential customers and businesses with as many as 100 users. In shop repair of PC and Mac hardware and software. Worked directly with customers over the phone, in store, and on site to establish and maintain a helpful and friendly professional relationship.

Designed and maintained brand new website for the company, from planning stages, through creating, and deployment. Wrote and sent a monthly newsletter to our network of 500+ customers. Created and supported multiple customer websites. Managed hosting and domains for many clients.

#### Education

San Jose State University Computer Science (2007 – 2011)